Mayonaka Punch currently has around
seven hundred thousand subscribers.
Seven hundred thousand...
There's one month and ten days
left until the deadline.
It should prove quite difficult for them
to reach a million subscribers in that time.
I see.
I shall continue to keep
an eye on their channel.
Starting Soon <3
Chat
Yukirinko Bot Starting soon <3
Snail Konyuki
azusa ah ah
konpeitou Hello
Len256 Hi! I've been waiting for this stream!
Yuyu Konyuki! What are you doing today?
I can't wait (>_<)/
Hello? Can you hear me?
Okay, looks good.
Sorry for barely making it in time!
Yukirinko here from the
Yukizuri Gaming Channel!
Konyuki!
Draculmania
Today, I'll be playing the 1988 Komachi title
Draculmania Perfect Cross,
the second game in the Draculmania series,
takomaru Never heard of it. But it sounds like fun.
KKK Is it a horror game?
The Manager Awesome, an endurance stream
anny We're in for a long night!
Snail The memories!!!!!
Tanaka_3 I've heard the name but never played it
calcium deficient i played draculmania so much
as a kid, but all i remember is how hard it was...
Fairy Child Thanks for the late night stream!
grass ball I'll be working with Yukizuri in the
background! All-nighter time
as an endurance stream until
I beat... the game...
New video from Mayonaka Punch
We Have a New Member
Rampage x Fateful Showdown!
MayoPan
Has a New
Member!
Stay Tuned for Updates!
Raise your hand if you know
why we're having this meeting.
Yes, Live?
The mysterious new MayoPan video that
got uploaded without our knowledge!
Exactly.
I privated it as soon as I could,
but a number of diehard fans saw,
and Sakura asked me about it.
Now, of all times, uploading a cheap-looking
video with only hiragana and no kanji?
Who could it be?
Hey, Ichiko!
It's totally you!
It's 100% you, Ichiko!
Y-You're barking up the wrong tree!
Oh, you can't whistle?
Let me show you how—
Ichiko.
What's the meaning of this?
I'm sorry!
I thought we'd get a huge boost in subs
if we brought on a new member!
Masaki-san, we're at fault here, too.
We knew how much pressure
Ichiko-chan was under.
Ichiko, the rest of us are
feeling the same pressure.
We're trying all sorts of ideas and
doing our best to shoot videos.
It's not enough!
We need something big, with lots of impact!
And since I knew Masaki used to be
a famous NewTuber...
Huh? Me?!
You wanted to bring Masaki on?!
Yes...
What do you mean, famous?
Trending NewTuber Gossip
Gossip Roundup of Hyped-Up Sisters Ex-Member Masakichi:
Real Name, Age, Public Controversy
They wrote up a gossip article.
They sure did.
She's getting hate comments.
- Public Outcry After Actions on Stream
The public response to Masakichi-san's
acts of violence
Here is a sample of how people felt
after this series of scandalous events.
achan @achanchan8420
I don't know much about Masakichi from Hype-Sis,
but there's no excuse for punching your colleague
on stream in front of a large audience.
Not to mention right in the face lol
She sure is.
Didn't I tell you I don't appear on camera?
But Live-sama said, "Masaki absolutely
wants to be in our videos!"
What?
If bringing you on can increase
our sub count even a little...
I'd rather stick to coming up with video ideas.
You can do that and star in our videos!
Y-You've all been together for a long time now.
Adding me into the mix would ruin the balance.
There never was a balance to begin with.
I mean, still...
Scandal.
"LOL at socking her out
after acting all chummy on camera."
"Booting Masakichi was the right move."
"Why does anyone like
watching her? She's so nasty."
Don't read them out loud!
I get comments like these all the time
from so-called Outside Kids fans!
Like, "Seriously though,
what kind of name is Tokage? LMAO."
Or, "Back in high school,
Tokage-san stole money from me."
Or, "Shut up, you're ugly as hell."
We're fellow hater targets!
This is the latest one.
Mio @ Outside Girl  1 week ago
I can't stand Tokage. To think she got to
breathe the same air as the Outside Kids.
Drop dead
"I can't stand Tokage."
"To think she breathed
the same air as the Outside Kids."
"Drop dead."
These guys are nothing more than pesky ants!
I'm a woolly mammoth,
so I'll crush them all I want!
Stomp! Stomp!
Anyway, I don't do on-camera—
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What?
You have something to say to me, do you not?
I came all this way, so out with it already.
Huh? Do we?
No clue.
It's too early for our blood supply.
Ah.
Does she mean the video?
Oh, the new member thing?
So that's it.
Um, is this about us adding a member?
Yes, it is.
Uh, we weren't going to add a human
who doesn't know about us or anything...
So you wanted a member
who knew all about your situation.
Announcing a new member
without their consent.
How so very inconsiderate of you.
Well...
That's got nothing to do with you,
does it, Shigeyuki-san?
Didn't I tell you to call me Yuki?
Besides, I believe it's got
plenty to do with me.
Hohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohoho
I'm so sorry!
I released that video without asking!
But...
I wanted to do something
to get more subscribers!
I see.
So you're hoping to invite someone
with a degree of popularity.
Yes...
So you found out about my secret.
Eh....?
Eh?
Namely, that I am Yukirinko,
the mega-famous gaming streamer!
Huh?
Gaming streamer?
It seems as though you wanted to
strong-arm me into joining your channel.
However, quite frankly, I must refuse!
It's true that I'd be a perfect fit,
but joining you as a new member...
No way!
Huh? What's going on?
I th-think...
Mm-hmm.
Whisper.
Whisper, whisper.
Mm-hmm.
Whisper, whisper, whisper.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, okay, I see.
Shigeyuki-san, you see...
Yuki.
You really don't need to worry!
We had zero intention of inviting you!
What?
It wasn't you!
Not at all!
What?
So please leave.
S-S-So that's it.
Yep.
Playing hard to get?
Nope.
It's not like you to be so modest.
That's not it.
The new member was going to be Masaki.
I can't believe you thought
we were trying to invite you.
I understand now.
Huh?
If you're going to be so stubborn,
I'm willing to wait until you
work up the courage to invite me!
N-N-N-No way!
I really thought their new member was me!
Um...
Can you not barge in like that?
This is my bedroom.
Yukizuri Gaming Channel
7244 subscribers
Found it!
Yukirinko? Really?
7,244 subscribers.
All she plays is ancient games!
Does Yuki-sama like playing games?
Yeah.
She once got so addicted,
she was incapable of doing anything else.
Which made Mother furious, and all
her games got destroyed... I thought.
When she gets into something,
she always ends up with tunnel vision.
MayoPan
Can you leave after you finish that?
Um, are you okay?
Well, that was an
embarrassing misunderstanding.
Real cringe-worthy...
Gloom...
H-Hey, cheer up!
Here, why don't you drink some of my blood?
Huh?
What? I thought my blood was tasty, right?
If you ask me, it's nothing special.
Don't be so conceited.
Oh, I see.
Man, seriously?!
That's so embarrassing!
In the past, I really liked video games.
She's starting a whole story now!
So after I began monitoring your channel,
when I came across a game streaming channel,
I wanted to give it a shot.
At first, I was satisfied with that.
But after seeing all of them
have fun at that festival...
You wanted to become
a part of it yourself, huh?
Streaming video games, huh?
I did consider trying it out for MayoPan...
In that case!
Let me show you how fun games can be!
What?
Okay!
That's a hard no on having Shige
come on as a member, agreed?
Agreed!
Yuki-sama can be a little scary.
I'm not giving up my slice of the profits.
Okay!
The courage to say no!
You know, if you want to join MayoPan...
I never said that.
Why not just be honest and ask?
I see no reason to ask,
and even if I were to ask,
I could never demean myself before Live.
What a pain in the ass.
What?
O-Oh, yeah...
What's the deal with you and Live?
The deal?
You two are always fighting.
That...
Continue        story
Start           story
Leave           room
would be a very, very long story.
Mother's blood runs strongest in Live and me,
making us both elite vampires.
On Mother's orders, we purged
the vampires who wished harm upon humans
and created an orderly world.
Back then, we were both rivals and comrades.
Thanks to our actions,
It became possible for humans
and vampires to coexist in peace.
And yet...
it became possible for humans
and vampires to coexist in peace.
And yet...
Mother
"Take this as a reward."
Yuki
"Thank you very much."
Live
"I want the one with a pendant!"
"Yoink!"
Yuki
"What?!"
"Wait, Live!"
Live betrayed me!
Yuki
"How could you?! Live!"
After that, every time we met...
Live "Shigeyuki, did you say something just now?"
Shigeyuki, did you say something just now?
Fine... Shigeyuki it is
I told you not to call me Shigeyuki!
Neener, neener! Shigeyuki, Shigeyuki!
Live "Neener, neener!
Shigeyuki, Shigeyuki!"
Need something from me?
Live "Need something from me?"
Nothing, really
Why don't we walk home together?
Live   "No, thanks. I think I'll go back
by myself tonight!"
No, thanks. I think I'll go back
by myself tonight!
She tore my heart into shreds.
So I made up my mind...
to part ways with Live!
That's what happened between Live and me.
What a flimsy tale!
So, like... I can't believe you still
want to join a channel with her.
After enough time, you manage
to tolerate a good deal of things.
Besides, she...
Live is fickle, irresponsible,
and a real handful,
but unlike me, who puts rules above all else,
she's honest about the things she likes.
That's the one part of her
I thought I could learn from.
Hey!
Can't you use the door?
Being honest about what you like...
Thank you very much.
We'll send over the final footage
for review before uploading.
Sure, thanks a lot.
Excuse me!
We sent you a message yesterday.
We're the Hyped-Up Sisters...
Wow, check out all that cheese!
It looks so good!
Let's eat, let's eat!
Get on with it.
Whoa, you're going for it!
Kicchomu, stop the camera.
Huh, why?
I cracked my lips when I went in for the bite!
What?!
It hurts!
Hey, I told you to moisturize them!
I don't have any lip balm.
Why not?!
What?
Oh, it's nothing.
You're filming with your phone?
Nowadays, we edit on our phones, too.
What about you?
We're doing an eating challenge
with these burgers.
You're back to NewTubing again?
That's right. Behind the scenes, that is.
You, behind the scenes?!
It came as a shock, even for me.
Tell us your channel name!
What's it called?
Um... Mayonaka Punch.
Wait, seriously?! MayoPan?!
No way!
Masaki, you're part of MayoPan?!
I mean, I was the one who started the channel.
Hold it!
Tell us more!
Ah, um...
Youber Eats delivery.
The burgers are here.
Is it time already?
Go wake Fu and Tokage so we can record.
Where's Masaki?
She's still not home yet.
Oh...
Really?!
Today's the day I hear your answer.
Good morning from the dead of night.
Mayonaka Pun—
Hey, there!
All of you watching the Mayonaka
Punch channel, nice to meet you!
Gaming streamer Yukirinko here!
Some of you must be surprised
to see Yukirinko's very first face reveal!
There's a real good reason for that, you see.
Actually, I'm going to be facing Live in an
eating contest to decide if I join MayoPan!
This was supposed to be
Live-sama's eating challenge.
Everything's changed. Every last bit.
If Live wins, I'll be officially
joining MayoPan!
On the other hand, if I win...
No matter how much the members
of MayoPan beg and plead,
I won't be joining as their new member!
I really don't get what's going on at all!
But it's all fine.
I just need to avoid winning!
This is one battle that
I can't afford not to lose!
What?
You've hired someone to
schedule appointments for you?!
We sure have.
You can even find people to
help you think up ideas for videos.
It's real handy.
We still edit our videos ourselves, at least.
Editing won't be easy to hire for,
since we want to preserve that unique charm.
It does take skills to convey that properly.
I see now.
MayoPan has way more subscribers,
so it's wild that you
handle it all by yourselves.
Hype-Sis is around, what, 300k now?
What if it is?
So you've been keeping up on us!
N-Not really!
Man, breaking up if you don't hit
a million subs, though?
Pretty bold to run with an idea
that could get you in hot water.
Was that supposed to be a dig at us?
And will you really break up
if you don't make it?
Well, if we don't reach it, the house
we all live in is going to be torn down.
The hell? How's that work?
Look, it's a really long story.
We were thinking of sending a
request to collab with MayoPan, too.
A collab? R-Really?!
MayoPan's really entertaining!
I hate to admit it, but you are.
O-Oh, is that right?
Hey, quit grinning!
I'm not.
You totally are!
Really, I'm not!
Stop lying! You are!
Really takes you back, doesn't it?
Hey, hey. Look over here.
You're recording?
Yeah, is that bad?
I don't mind.
It's been so long, so what's the harm?
Masaki?
I'll have to pass!
My face looks awful right now!
What? Isn't it a little late for that?
It's fine!
You look the same as always!
Shut up! I do not!
Get her, Kicchomu!
Cut it out, you dumb gorilla!
What was that?!
My hand!
My hand's cramping up!
Eat like you mean it!
I was raised with good manners.
Now it's my right hand!
Let's take a break for some tea.
Th-This is such a colossal waste of time.
Everything's changed. Every last bit.
Okay, if I feel like it,
I'll let you collab with MayoPan!
So work hard for it!
Whawuzzat?!
We may have fewer subscribers,
but we have some real hardcore fans!
Some are a little too hardcore.
Right?
Hey, Masaki.
Can we use the video we shot earlier?
Hey...
Was my face all tensed up?
What?
Not at all.
I see...
I see.
I, Masakichi!
Hereby swear to be honest about what I like!
Hey!
Not so loud!
With that, I bid you farewell!
What's that mean?
Dunno.
I did it!
I was on camera!
Live! I'll star in our videos!
What?
I-I did it...
I won.
And so, the winner of
the eating contest is Live!
As much as it pains me to say it...
I'll be joining MayoPan!
What the hell?
Isn't that nice, Ichiko-chan?
Masaki-san said she'll join.
Everything went exactly as planned!
Come, let us record the video where I join.
You've got nerves of steel, huh?
Shige, out of the way.
What?!
I told you to show up on camera
when I say, "These are our new members!"
Call me Yuki!
Wait, no, Yukirinko!
Just remember, the real highlight here
is Masaki joining MayoPan.
Make sure you don't get
in the way, Yukirinko-san!
Don't be absurd.
The main attraction here is me!
Hohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohohoho
Masaki!
What took you so long?
Oh, I just got a little overexcited.
We finally get to be on video together!
I'm so thrilled!
It's time for the big climax on our
road to reach one million subscribers!
Let's kick it up one last time!
Hey, c'mon, Shige!
You're one of us now,
so try and join in for times like this.
The comments.
What?
They're utter chaos.
See?
Ruka  1 day ago
Is Masakichi really involved with them?
5 replies
Delhi Amano  1 day ago
Masakichi? Who's that?
This sucks
Honey Lemon  1 day ago
Ichiko-chan, get away from that abusive woman!
Yuki
Sent you a sticker
Goodnight
100-Hour Nonstop Livestream
Wait, wait!
What the hell's going on?!
No need to make a fuss.
It's just the famous gaming
streamer Yukirinko joining MayoPan!
Not that!
What?
I'm asking what's gonna happen to me!
Well...
Next time: "Announcement: Gone Missing."
Announcement: Gone Missing
Currently Missing
That's one alarming title!